A Guide to the Papers of the Stuart-Baldwin Families, 1764-1884
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
Papers of the Stuart-Baldwin Families 1764-1884
Special Collections, University of Virginia Library
228
This collection consists of ca. 4,500 items (19 Hollinger boxes, ca. 8 linear shelf feet).
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
There are no restrictions.
Acquisition Information
This collection was deposited in the University of Virginia Library by Archibald G. Robertson of Richmond, Virginia, on October 21, 1938. The collection was given to the University of Virginia Library on June 27, 1980, by Mrs. Marvyn W. Robertson of Richmond, Virginia; John S. Beard of Shillington, Pennsylvania; Archibald G. Robertson of Richmond, Virginia; Alexander F. Robertson, Jr., of Staunton, Virginia; George M. Cochran of Staunton, Virginia; Alexander R. Beard of St. Davids, Pennsylvania; and Margaret Cochran Hinch of Staunton, Virginia.
Biographical/Historical Information
Archibald Stuart was born on March 19, 1757, in Staunton, Virginia, the son of Alexander and Mary (Patterson) Stuart. He was educated at the Augusta Academy, the College of William and Mary, and studied law with Thomas Jefferson following the American Revolution. He then began practicing law in the Shenandoah Valley and served as a judge of the General court of Virginia from 1800 until just before his death.
Stuart was also active in politics as a leader of the Jeffersonian Democrats in Virginia. He was elected to the Virginia House of Delegates from Botetourt County in 1783 and was particularly active in the reform of the state court system and the reorganization of state government. He also played a prominent role in the ratification of the new federal Constitution in 1788, was a member of the Virginia-Kentucky Boundary Commission in 1795, a member of the Virginia Senate at the turn of the century, and was a presidential elector for the Jeffersonian Democrats from 1800 to 1824. Stuart married Eleanor Briscoe, the daughter of Gerard Briscoe of Frederick County, Virginia, in May, 1791, and died in Staunton on July 11, 1832.
Briscoe Gerard Baldwin was born on January 18, 1789, in Winchester, Virginia, the eldest son of Cornelius Baldwin and Mary Briscoe, another daughter of Gerard Briscoe. He attended William and Mary College and later studied law under Judge William Daniel in Cumberland County, Virginia. During 1818-1820 he served in the Virginia House of Delegates as representative for Augusta County; and, in 1829-1830 was a member of the constitutional convention. He returned to the House of Delegates during 1841-1842. On January 29, 1842, Baldwin was elected a member of the Supreme Court of Appeals of Virginia and held that position until his death on May 18, 1852.
Scope and Content Information
This collection consists of ca. 4,500 items (19 Hollinger boxes, ca. 8 linear shelf feet), 1764-1884, the papers of Archibald Stuart (1757-1832) and Briscoe Gerard Baldwin (1789-1852) of Staunton, Virginia. The collection is comprised chiefly of correspondence and legal and financial papers pertaining to the legal practice of Archibald Stuart and Briscoe G. Baldwin. These papers concern various legal issues, including land patents, wills, land deeds, land surveys, accounts, slave transactions, and criminal and civil suits. Also included in the collection are letters from Martha S. Baldwin to her husband, Briscoe G. Baldwin, containing news of family and friends, and correspondence of Alexander Hugh Holmes Stuart, son of Archibald Stuart, some of which concerns the Whig party and Presidential elections.
Also included in the collection are military papers, primarily signed oaths to serve in the Continental Army, 1782-1783, and documents verifying military service for pensions. Other topics mentioned in the collection include student life at the College of William and Mary, Virginia Military Institute, and the University of Virginia; temperance parties; a law school operated by Briscoe G. Baldwin in Staunton; and meetings of the Virginia Assembly. There is also a copy of a land grant signed by Thomas Jefferson and an answer to a bill of complaint given by John Wayles as an attorney in the case of Faroll and Jones vs Horbort. Principal correspondents include Archibald Stuart, Briscoe G. Baldwin, Martha S. Baldwin, Alexander Hugh Holmes Stuart, and John Brown, Baldwin's father-in-law. Other correspondents include Charles Francis Adams, Philip Pendleton Barbour, James Breckinridge, Arthur Spicer Brockenbrough, William H. Cabell, Augustus Alexander Chapman, William Daniel, Jr., James H. Dooley, Thomas Walker Gilmer, Chapman Johnson, George Tucker and Henry St. George Tucker.
Organization
This collection is arranged chronologically, within two series: Series I: Correspondence and Series II: Legal and Financial Papers, including Miscellaneous Papers. A checklist has been prepared of the correspondence and is arranged in alphabetical order by last name of correspondent.
Index to Correspondents
Only letters written by the following correspondents are included in this list, not letters written to them.
Abbot, Joseph re renting a plantation (1819 Mar 2)
Abbot, Sinclair (1825 Nov 6)
Adams, Charles F., Jr. (1871 Feb 17)
Ahl, Peter (1798 Mar 22)
Alexander, Andrew re his son attending B.G. Baldwin's law school (1837 Oct 1)
Alexander, Archibald Macon re attending B.G. Baldwin's law school (1831 Jul 11)
Alexander, Henry (1821 Aug 11; 1833 May 21, Oct 13)
Alexander, William (re Thomas Adam Estate 1790 Sep 8) & (1791 Feb 21)
[Allemong], John (1832 Oct 26)
Allen, Guy R. C. (1840 Nov 28; 1842 Jan 1)
Allen, James (1838 May 10, Jun 16)
Allen, James D. (1834 July 7; 1836 Dec 25; 1841 Sep 8)
Allen, John (re his health 1796 May 19)
Allen, Joseph (1825 Feb 25; 1839 May 23)
Allen, John James, 1797-1871, (1844 Aug 19, 25, and Oct 9 re the death of his father, birth of a son, and his wife's illness)
Allen, Robert, 1794-1859, (1831 Apr 8)
Allen, William H. (1839 Apr 8)
Alverson, John (1826 Jun 29)
Anderson, Alexander (1848 Sep 1)
Anderson, John T. (1835 Oct 16; 1841 Aug 23)
Anderson, Robert re deposition of William Anderson (1824 Nov 1)
Anderson, William (1815 May 30; 1826 Aug 17)
Anthony, James B. (1838 Jul 14; 1846 Dec 30; 1847 Jul 17)
Anthony, Mark (1819 Nov 26)
Arbuckle, Mathew (1837 Nov 19; 1840 Sep 23)
Archer, William B. (1841 Oct 29)
Archer, William Segar, 1789-1855, (1839 Sep 10; 1841 Apr 7)
Arthur, T.G. re the election of B.G. Baldwin as Honorary Member of the Literary Society (1839 Nov 25)
Ast, John H. (1848 Mar 10)
Atkinson, Thomas D. (1820 Nov 13)
Atkisson, John (1834 Nov 1)
Auld, Colin re records of Breckenridge vs Auld (1839 Sep 23)
Austin, A.M. (1838 Jun 11)
Bagby, Thomas (1845 Apr 14)
Bailey, Edward B. (1831 Sep 13; 1837 Dec 16)
Bailey, James H. (1838 Dec 6)
Bailey, William (1836 Oct 24; 1838 Feb 27)
Baker (Cornelius) & Co., New York (1838 Jan 3 & 20)
Baker, Henry (1837 Feb 16)
Baldwin, Dr. Archibald S. (1822 Dec 9; 1824 Apr 28; 1835 Apr 7, Jul 26, Aug 28; 1836 Jan 28; 1840 Jun 1, Oct 17)
Baldwin, Alexander G. (1831 Feb 17, Jun 2; 1832 Aug 14; 1834 Aug 13; 1835 Feb 16, Jun 10; 1847 May 7)
Baldwin, Briscoe (son of B.G. Baldwin) at Virginia Military Institute (1833 Jun 18; ca. 1835 Dec 18; ca. 1836 Jun 23; ca. 1839 Mar 21; 1845 Nov 29; 1846 Oct 28; 1847 Apr 26; 1848 May 6)
Baldwin, Briscoe Gerard (1818 Sep 2; Nov 28; 1820 Feb 17; Nov 23; 1822 Jan 27, with earlier part of letter, 1821 Dec 7 included; 1825 Aug 15; 1829 Sep 29; 1833 Jun 22; 1836 Dec 14; 1838 Sep 15; 1842 Jan 12; 1844 Jul 28, Oct 15, Nov 17; and n.y. Feb, Jul 19, Nov 7, 13, 17)
Baldwin, C. Briscoe (1838 Jul 17, 31, Nov 2, 14)
Baldwin, C.C. (1836 Jan 30, Dec; 1837 Jun 21, Dec 30; 1839 Aug 13, Nov 7, Dec 17); 1840 Feb 15, Jun 6, Sep 26; 1841 Jan 23, May 17, Oct 18; 1842 Jun 1, 26, Aug 15; 1873 Oct 29)
Baldwin, Charles R. (1832 Jun 10, Nov 3; 1835 May 11)
Baldwin, Hugh H. (1835 Jan 10)
Baldwin, Isaac H. (1835 June 1)
Baldwin, J.W. (ca. 1840)
Baldwin, James (1846 Feb 16, Oct 24; 1847 Jan 12)
Baldwin, John Brown, 1820-1873, (re his education 1836 Sep 12; ca. 1837 Jan 14; ca. 1837 Apr 24 (re losing his election); 1841 Jul 23, 28, Sep 17; account of his travels and sessions of Congress 1842 Feb 16; 1842 Oct 11, 1843 Nov 13; 1844 Aug 12; enclosure with an account of a Whig meeting, 1844 Aug 30; 1845 Jan 7, Apr 25; 1846 Nov 10; 1847 Jul 16; Major McCue refuses Baldwin's commission as a Colonel of the 160th Regiment, 1848 Apr 5; 1848 Apr 22, Jul 25)
Baldwin, Joseph (1853 Nov 21)
Baldwin, Joseph C. (1825 Feb 12; 1826 Mar 23;1841 Oct 10)
Baldwin, Joseph Glover (1815-1864) (re estate of Judge Holmes & Clover Dale in 1836 Jul 9; Sep 10; 1837 Jan 9, Apr; 1838 Aug 15; 1839 Jan 9)
Baldwin, Martha S. to her husband, Judge B.G. Baldwin (1820 Apr 17; 1825 Aug 15; [1829] Apr 17; 1832 Aug 11; 1833 Jul 24; 1834 Apr, Jul 18, Dec 28; 1835 Feb 20; Aug 31, Oct 29; ca. 1835; 1836 May 4, Aug 3,Oct 25; 1838 Apr 18, 24, Jul 29, Oct 27; 1839 Apr 13; 1840 Jan 10, Aug 23; ca. 1840; 1842 Jan 12, Apr 1, 10, 21; Jul 13, 28; Sep 11; 1843 Jul 19, 31; Aug 3 with an account of the fire; 1844 Jan 22, 29; Feb 13, 24 re birth of granddaughter, 29; Jul 28; Aug 8, 30, Oct 15, 27; ca. 1844; 1845 Jan 12, 24; Feb 11, 26, Aug 6, 14, 30; Sep 12; 1846 Feb 8; ca. 1846 Aug 1; n.y. Feb; Jul 19; Nov 7, 13, & 17 )
Baldwin, Robert T. (1835 Sep 26)
Ballard, John (1820 Jul 24 re his name stricken from the Pension List)
Banks, Linn (1820 Oct 28)
Barbour, James (1775-1842) (1841 Mar 5)
Barbour John Strode (1790- 1833) (re attending law school 1832 Nov 27)
Barbour, Philip Pendleton (1783-1841) (letter of introduction for Richard C. Derby 1836 May 8)
Barclay, E.S. (1833 Sep 16)
Barley, Samuel (1838 Dec 3)
Barraud, Otway Byrd (1801- ?) (1840 Sep 22 re Democratic Whig Club of Norfolk)
Barton, R.C.P. (1817 Aug 28 results of an experiment made to ascertain the properties of a piece of plaster)
Baxter, Sidney S. (1834 Aug 15 & 21; 1837 Apr 16, Jun 2; 1838 Apr 16; ca. 1840)
Beale, Charles (1841 May 27)
Beale, John (1808 Aug 20)
Bell, Samuel (1839 Oct 26)
Berkeley, [Edmund?] (1842 Jul 28)
Berry, Henry (1840 Oct 30)
Berry, Laurence (1809 Apr 10; Jun 18; 1810 Mar 20; Jun 5; 1811 Jun 4; 1812 Apr 14; 1816 Feb 26; 1817 Feb 17 re debts of father of Archibald Stuart; Sep 22; Nov 15; 1818 May 18; 1819 Mar 1; Nov 26)
Berry, Samuel (1833 Oct 7 re suit of Berry's heirs)
Beverley, Robert (1790 Jun 30; 1791 Aug 13; Sep 3; 1797 Aug 26; 1798 Sep 2; 1799 Feb 18; 1801 Jan 30; Jul 6)
Bilbro, Benjamin (1828 Apr 13)
Bill, John (1789 Mar 15)
Billups, Thomas C. (1831 Apr 12; Jul 2; 1832 May 1; Oct 19; 1833 Jan 25; Sep 14; Nov 4; 1834 Jul 20; Oct 31; 1835 Oct 5; 1836 Mar 27; Sep 28; 1837 Feb 24; Mar 17; Nov 11; 1838 Oct 28; 1843 Feb 20)
Billups, William (ca. 1831 Mar; 1832 Aug 20; 1833 Nov 27)
Bird, Mark (1837 Oct 24)
Blackburn, Ann (re husband's estate 1836 May 28)
Blackburn, Samuel (1833 Apr 26; 1834 Jan 23; 1836 Mar 29)
Blackeley, Alexander (1836 Oct)
Blount, William (re Colonel King's Iron Works? 1797 Apr 21)
Booz, H. (1836 Oct 12)
Bowling & Haynie, Front Royal, Virginia (re patent for wheat machine 1839 Aug 8)
Bowyer, Henry (1816 Jun 14, n.d.)
Bowyer, J.W. (1796 Jan 25)
Bowyer, John (1824 Dec 15)
Bowyer, Lucian (1831 May 29)
Bowyer, Peter G. (1814 Dec 3)
Bowyer, Strather (1814 Jul 26)
Bowyer, William C. (1814 Apr 13; Jul 19; Aug 14; Sep 16, & Sep; 1815 Mar 14; Jul 14; Aug 18; 1818 Mar 21; Jun 14; 1819 Jun 13; Aug 31; Sep 3, 14, 20; 1835 Apr 23 & 28; Sep 29; 1836 Apr 29; Oct 1 & 11; 1838 Apr 3)
Boyd, A.L. (1837 Mar 11)
Boyd, Elisha (1822 Mar 22; Apr 19; Aug 23; 1824 Jan 6; Sep 6; Oct 29)
Boyd, Thomas J. (1838 Feb 8 & 28)
Boyd, William W. (1837 Mar 11; Sep 21; 1841 Feb 11; May 14)
Boyden, Ebenezer, 1803-1891, (1834 Apr 14; 1836 Feb 15)
Bradby, James A. (1786 Oct 6)
Bradley, Orville (invitation to Whig celebration 1840 Aug 11)
Bradley, Solomon C. (1834 Dec 13 & 15)
Bratten, Robert (1831 Mar 9; 1836 Jan 15)
Breckinridge, Cary (1838 Aug 17; 1841 Jan 8)
Breckinridge, James, 1763-1833, (1816 Aug 27, 2 items; 1821 Dec 16)
Breedlove, Isaac (1820 Aug 8)
Brockenbrough, Arthur Spicer, 1780-1832, (1831 Jan 27; Feb 3)
Brockenbrough, John White (1838 Nov 8; 1839 Mar 23; Apr 27; 1840 Feb 27)
Brodhead, Daw, Jr. (1792 Mar 17; Apr 25)
Brown, Alexander, 1796-1864, (1819 Jun 18; Sep 9; Nov 15; 1821 Mar 31; May 19; Nov 20; 1822 Oct 2)
Brown, Bernard (1825 Oct 16)
Brown, J.E. (1844 Nov 17)
Brown, J.W. (1814 Mar 13; Sep 2; ca. 1814)
Brown, James Edwin (1814 Sep 2; 1828 Jan 6; 1833 Sep 14; 1834 Dec 23; 1835 Aug 30; Sep 26; Nov 10; 1836 Jan 7; 1837 Apr 28; 1838 Mar 22; May 15; Sep 25; 1839 Aug 20; re congratulations on Baldwin becoming Judge of the Court of Appeals, 1842 Feb 28; condolences on the death of B.G. Baldwin's daughter, Peggy Baldwin, 1844 Apr 16; 1845 Oct 21)
Brown, James (1792 Aug 21)
Brown, John, 1762-1826, (1786 Oct 2; 1819 Aug 31; Sep 3, 20; 1820 Jan 18 is oversize letter)
Brown, John, Jr. (1838 Mar 19)
Brownlee, James (1836 Nov 15)
Bryan, Allan C. (1835 Oct 4)
Bryan, Edward, Jr. (1834 Mar 12; 1838 Jan 30)
Buchear, Jacob (1824 Aug 27)
Buck, Marcus C. (1834 Oct 28)
Buck, Thomas (1835 Apr 16)
Bullitt, Cuthbert (1814 Sep 20; 1824 Jan 4; Feb 14; Apr 22)
Bullitt, Cuthbert & Thomas (1814 Feb 16; Jun 22; Jul 12; Aug 6 & 9; Sep 20; 1815 Feb 20; Mar 6; May 17; Jun 15; Jul 3 & 28; Oct 2; 1816 Feb 12 & 22; May 2; Jul 22; Dec 6; 1817 Feb 5; Mar 19; Aug 29; 1819 May 20; Jul 20; 1820 Apr 2; Jul 1; 1822 Mar 3; 1823 Mar 26)
Bullit, Thomas (1814 Sep 3; 1819 Mar 7)
Burgess, Joel (1822 Sep 3)
Burton, P.P. (1836 Feb 25)
Buster, Claudius (1830 Jul 2; 1832 Nov 7; 1833 May 30; Nov 22; Dec 16 & 29
1834 Jan 12 & 15; Feb 18; Mar 11; Apr 8; May 20; Jul 11; 1835 Jul 23, 2 items; 1836 May 27; 1839 Jul 13)
Buster, James S. (1838 Apr 28; Nov 2)
Button, Charles W. (1873 Feb 11)
Byrd, Peter (1834 Feb 9 re his house having burned down, 2 items)
Cabell, Mayo (1845 Jun 16)
Cabell, William H., 1772-1853, (ca. 1835)
Cail, David (1786 Nov 4)
Caldwell, A. (1836 Apr 26)
Calhoun, William B. (1835 Dec 17; 1836 Aug 29)
Callaghan, Oliver (1839 Feb 18)
Calwell, William B. (1833 Jun 4; Sep 29; 1839 Apr 15; Dec 28)
Campbell, James (1787 Mar 10)
Campbell, John (1788 Nov 11; 1823 Apr 3; Aug 8)
Caperton, Allen T., 1810- ?, (1837 Apr 7 & 20; 1838 Jan 18)
Caperton, Hugh (1821 Aug 11; 1832 Oct 27)
Caperton, Lewis E. (1839 Sep 12)
Carlile, John S. (1836 Sep 27; 1837 Feb 21; 1842 Aug 5)
Carr, James L. (1838 Jun 8)
Carr, James Overton, d. 1864, (1833 Nov 21; 1834 Jul 7; 1836 Dec 25; 1837 Jan 18; 1841 Oct 9)
Carr, William (1841 Jan 24)
Carrol, John (1843 Oct 17)
Carter, D. (1833 Jul 15)
Carter, Robert (1835 May 16)
Cartmill, Thomas (1842 Mar 22)
Cartmill & Wood (1820 Nov 19; 1821 Mar 21; 1834 Feb 22; Jun 15; 1835 Oct 26)
Caruthers, Isaac (1819 Sep 25)
Caruthers, James (1790 Nov 27)
Catlett, Henry (1836 Aug 2; Sep 27; Oct 27)
[Caupi ?], J. (1832 May 14)
Chambers, M. (1834 Aug 3; 1835 Mar 21)
Chapin, C. (1840 Sep 3; Nov 26)
Chapman, Augustus Alexander, 1805-1876, (1840 Jan 5; Mar 4; Jun 5; 1841 Mar 5; Jun 23)
Charlton, William B. (results of an election in Pulaski County, Virginia, 1841 Apr 23)
Chisney, Jamison (1791 Apr 7)
Christian, William (1828 Mar 13)
Chrisman, John (1835 Jan 22)
Clagett, R.H. (1842 Sep 30)
Clark, John A. (1840 Aug 15)
Clarke, John (1818 Aug 17; 1822 Mar 19)
Clarke, Samuel (1829 Sep 17)
Clarke, Thomas (re the Whigs 1837 Dec 23; 1839 Nov 12)
Clarkson, R.G.H. (1842 Mar 12)
Clayton, William (1833 May 4; Jul 24)
Clelland, R.W. (1853 Aug 15)
Clendinen, George (1791 Jan 21)
Cloyd, Gordon (1815 Apr 7)
Coalter, Judge (1831 Mar 17)
Coalter, John, 1771-1838, (1805 Nov 1; 1831 Jul 15 & 28; 1832 Oct 29; 1833 Mar 27)
Coalter, William B. (1819 Mar 1; 1831 Apr 12)
Cochran, James A. (1837 Oct 14)
Cocke, John R. (ca. 1836, 2 invitations; ca. 1838 Mar 19; 1842 Mar 11; Jun 28; 1844 May 8; ca. 1844; 1845 May 14)
[Cockiall], Samuel (1824 Sep 21)
Coleman, N.B. (1830 Jul 18)
Conrad, Robert G. (1836 Oct 12; 1866 Jun 29)
Cook, Giles (1840 Aug 31)
Cook, Robert L. (1840 Feb 18)
Cooke, William D. (1842 Oct 10; 1843 Oct 2)
Cowan, Joseph (1826 Apr 1)
Cowan, Robert (1841 Sep 1)
Cowan, William (1796 Sep 5)
Coyner, A.H. (1838 Aug 15)
Coyner, Martin (1839 May 8)
Coyner, Robert (1834 Dec 22; 1835 Dec 31)
Craig, John (1791 Jan 7 re William Crow estate)
Craig, John J. (1837 Apr)
Craik, James, 1730-1840, (1834 Apr 25)
Crawford, Hugh J. (1845)
Crawford, James (1821 Mar 1; 1835 Jul 15)
Crosby, J. (1837 Jun 5, Jul 1)
Crow, William (1791 Jul 4)
Crowell, John (1790 Feb 2)
Crump, William (1833 May 7)
Crutchfield, Thomison (1822 Jun 1, mentions the death of a slave in Fincastle by a whipping)
Culton, Joseph W. (1834 Jan 11; Oct 14)
Cummings & Barclay, Clarksville (1833 Sep 16)
Cunningham, Jonathan (1829 Aug 19)
Cuthall, A.K.W. (1799 Jun 21)
Dabney, C. (1831 Jun 30)
Dade, Lawrence T. (1832 Nov 29)
Daingerfield, J.F. (1833 Jan 1; 1834 Jan 21)
Daniel, Peter Vyvian, 1784-1860, (1831 Sep 1)
Daniel, Raleigh Travers, 1805-1877, (re the Whig State Convention, 1840 Sep 21)
Daniel, William, Jr. (1833 Mar 28; Oct 22; Nov 20; 1835 Jul 14; Oct 15; 1837 Oct 16; 1841 Feb 4; 1846 Dec 21)
Daniel, William P. (1830 Dec 30)
Davenport, Allen & Co., Richmond (1838 Jan 29)
Davidson, E.J. (1839 Oct 10)
Davidson, James D. (1833 Aug 1; 1836 Jul 23;1841 May 18; Jun 19; 1842 Sep 29; 1844 Jun 26)
Davis, Abraham W. (1831 May 26)
Davis, George (1792 Jul 6)
Davis, Jordan & Co., Lexington (suit re the Bath Iron Works 1835 Jul 1)
Davis, Micajah, Jr. (1841 Mar 10)
Day, Edward (1817 Jun 6; Sep 25; 1818 Jan 31)
Dean, T. (1835 Jul 30 re death of A.G. Baldwin)
Deane, F.B., Jr. (re coal and iron trade 1842 Jan 10)
Decker, Levi (1822 Sep 10)
Delong, George (1832 Mar 15; 1834 May 14)
Dillard, A. (1833 Aug 26)
Dillard, Henry (1833 Dec 5; 1834 Mar 10; Apr 28; May 17; Jul 22; Aug 28; Dec 2; 1835 May 23; 1836 Jul 24)
Dold, Samuel M. (1838 Jan 1)
Donaghe, Hugh (1789 May 22)
Donaghe, William W. (1815 Dec 18)
Donnally, Andrew (1789 ___ 10; 1834 Jan 4)
Donoho, Thomas (1830 Jul 17)
Dooley, James H. (1874 Jul 6)
Dorman, Charles P. (1825 Oct 4; 1833 Nov 5; 1838 Feb 26; 1840 Oct 27; 1841 Nov 25; 1844 Jul 27)
Dorman & Davidson (1839 Jul 2)
Douglas, John (1826 Jul 11)
Dougherty, Isaiah (1835 Aug 9; Sep 22)
Douthat, William H. (1838 Jan 3; Jul 31; 1839 Jan 19; 1841 Nov 15)
Dowdall, P.B. (1835 Feb 23)
Doyle, J. (1840 Jul 8)
Doyle, R. (1831 May 7)
Drake, Joseph (1834 Jan 6)
Dudley, Richard H. (1839 May 8)
Duffield, W.C. (1833 Jul 30)
Dufield, Benjamin (1831 Jul 22)
Dunbar, Ephraim (1821 Feb 28)
Dunbar, John R.W. (1831 Jun 8; 1832 Oct 17)
Dunscomb, Andrew, 1757?-1802, (1791 Jan; Mar 27)
Dupew, Joseph (1834 Jun 11)
Duval, William (n.d.)
Dyer, T. (1836 Sep 3)
Eagon, Samson (1824 Jan 26)
Early, Samuel H. (1835 Oct 21)
Eason, John G. (1831 Nov 4; 1832 Sep 14)
Edington, Edmund (1816 Jun 7; Aug 27; 1817 Jan 12; 1818 Apr 5)
Edmonson, David (1838 Aug 20)
Edwards, James L. (1820 Jul 24 & 25)
Effinger, Michael (1838 May 8; 1840 Jul 1; 1841 Jan 13; 1842 Jun 22)
Effinger, Peter (1842 Jun 10)
Elliott, E.T. (1834 Sep 1; 1835 Aug 13)
Ellis, V. (1836 Jul 29)
Emmons, William (1831 Feb 22)
Erskine, William (1826 Nov 26)
Erskine & Eickelberger (1835 Nov 12; 1838 May 10)
Eskridge, Alexander P. (1834 Sep 30; Dec 13; 1835 Jun 10; 1839 Sep 25; 1840 Mar 13)
Eskridge, George (1842 Aug 4)
Eskridge, M.F. (1845 Feb 18)
Eskridge, William S. (ca. 1818; 1828 Apr 29; 1837 Apr 13; 1841 Apr 1; Dec 2 & 4; 1842 Feb 4 re congratulations on Baldwin becoming Judge of the Court of Appeals & 1842 Feb 19; Mar 3; Apr 23; 1843 Jan 30; 1845 Dec 16; 1847 Jan 14)
Estill, B. (1836 Jun 18; Aug 18)
Estill, Dr. H. H. (1836 Oct 24)
Estill, John M. (1839 May 8)
Evans, Thomas (1821 Mar 1)
Evirett, Joseph (1799 May 26)
Ewing, Thomas, 1789-1871, (1842 Feb 12)
Feay, John (1837 Apr 5)
Feay, Levi (1820 Jan 20)
Fechtig, C.C. (1833 Oct 14)
Ferrell, Robert (1838 Jun 13, 28; Jul 18)
Field, R.H. (1841 Jun 21, 30)
Finley, Samuel (1836 Dec 17)
Fizer, Samuel (1834 Sep 23)
Fletcher, Richard P. (1837 Jun 13)
Fletcher, Thomas C. (1817 Apr 9)
Foster, John (1836 Feb 9)
Foster, N. (1825 Jan 10)
Fox, Jane (1832 Nov 8; 1833 Jan 3; 1834 May 13; Jun 11)
Francisco, Charles F. (1841 Nov 9)
Francisco, Charles L. (1835 Apr 28)
Frankeberger, Joel (1829 Mar 21; 1831 Jun 11)
Fray, John (1838 Jan 30)
Frazier, William (1848 Jan 12, 20)
Fry, J.N. (1819 May 8)
Fuller, George W. (1852 Jul 30)
Fulton, John (1809 Jan 17)
Galladay, David (1812 Aug 5)
Gambill, H.J. (1827 Aug 25; 1837 May 24; 1838 Aug 31; 1839 Feb 27)
Gambill, W.W. (1791 Jan 16)
Gamble, James C. (1825 Oct 27)
Gamble, Samuel (1829 Mar 21)
Garber, W.H. (1837 Feb 16)
Gardner, John (n.d.)
Gaunt, Joseph (1834 Jul 30)
Gibson, George R. (1831 Sep 16)
Gibson, James (1825 Nov 8)
Gillespie, William A. (1840 Aug 18)
Gilmer, J.H. (1846 May 12)
Gilmer, Thomas Walker (1834 Jun 27; 1835 Jun 16, Oct 16, Nov 20, Dec 3; 1838 Jun 16)
Gilmore, A[ddison] (1836 Nov 11)
Givens, Alexander (1828 Mar 8)
Givens, Joseph (1823 Sep 5)
Glass, James V. (1836 Jul 24)
Gold, James (1836 Apr 16; 1837 Sep 23; 1840 May 13; 1844 Sep 17, Dec 23; 1845 Jan 6)
Good, M.C. (1839 Feb 25)
Gosling, Palmer (1839 Jun 14)
Graham, James (1829 Sep 29)
Graham, Robert (1794 Dec 8; 1796 Dec 15)
Graham, William (1791 Mar 28)
Grattan, Peachy R. (1833 June 20; 1834 Nov 15; 1838 Nov 26; 1840 May 23; 1846 Jun 24)
Grattan, R., Jr. (1839 Mar 5)
Graves, Tarleton W. (1836 Feb 9)
Gray, John (1839 Jun 22)
Gray, Robert (1832 Dec 29)
Grayson, R.O. (1813 Dec 17)
Grayson, William (1828 May 6)
Green, Eliza Ann (1833 Dec 30; 1834 May 7; 1835 May 15)
Greenlee, D. (1836 July 1)
Greiner, John F. (1840 Apr 24)
Grider, H. (1840 Sep 10 the Whigs of Warren County)
Griffin, John H. (1841 Aug 2)
Guthrie, H.G. (1838 Jun 2)
Guthrie, William (1838 Jun 2)
Gwathmey, Samuel (1824 May 31, Sep 4; 1825 Sep19)
Gwatkin, Charles A. (1839 Jul 20; 1841 Feb 27; 1842 Feb 8, Apr 1)
Hall, Alexander, L. (1819 Oct 30)
Hall, Alexander S. (1844 Feb 2)
Hall, Benjamin (1802 Jan 16; 1806 Jun 25)
Hall, James (1832 Dec 10)
Hall, John (1790 Feb 21, Mar 19, May 27)
Hall, N.K. (1871 Feb 20; 1872 Jun 21)
Hall, Peter (1791 Mar 29)
Hall, Thomas (1786 Sep 20; n.d.)
Hammond, George W. (1836 Sep 27; 1840 Dec 3)
Hancock, George (1838 Sep 8)
Hancock, Newby (1828 Sep 15)
Hannah, Patterson (1820 Aug 26)
Hardin, W.D. (1815 Nov 23)
Harman, L. (1836 Mar 29)
Harper, Kenton (1839 Jul 5)
Harris, G.W., Dr. (1834 Mar 3)
Harrison, Benjamin (1795 Dec 20)
Harrison, George W. (1816 Oct 16; 1818 Nov 1)
Hay, William (1787 Dec 20; 1788 Dec 15; 1790 Aug 4)
Hazlett, Robert (1835 Jul 17)
Hebb, George (1831 May 8; 1832 Jan 31, Jul 30; 1833 Jun 14; 1834 Dec 24; 1835 Jul 21; 1836 May 24)
Hebertson, Heiskells, & Hoskins (1837 Apr 24)
Hedrick, David (1833 May 25)
Heiskell, William H. (1838 Nov 16)
Hendel, William, Rev. (1817 Mar 6)
Henderson, A.J. (1837 Sep 25)
Hendry, Ann (1833 Nov 11)
Hening, William Waller (1791 Sep 23)
Heron, J. (1790 Apr 2)
Herron, Walter (1834 Apr 25, Aug 29, Oct 27)
[Hick], [W.] [A.] (1839 Jul 26)
Hill, James T. (1839 Aug 2)
Hill, Reuben D. (1833 Dec 28; 1838 Feb 16)
Hill, Richard J. (1838 Mar 31)
Hite, Abraham (1791 Dec 3)
Hix, Joseph (1822 Jul 6)
Hix, Patrick (1835 Oct 21)
Hoff, Lewis (1826 Sep 26)
Hoffman, Daniel (1835 Sep)
Hoge, John (1799 Aug 11)
Hogsett, William E. (1834 May 26)
Hogshead, John W. (1836 Mar 25)
Holmes, D. (1795 Dec 22)
Holmes, Joseph (1792 June 9)
Holt, J. (1845 Mar 19)
Hope, James T. (1838 Jan 28)
Hopkins, J. (1834 Mar 22)
Hopkins, Philip (1836 Mar 7)
Howard, Benjamin (1807 Dec 29)
Hoys, J. (1821)
Hudson, Robert M. (1836 May 13)
Hughart, Thomas (1786 Sep 20)
Hull, David G. (1833 Nov)
Hull, Peter (1791 Mar 29)
Humphrys, S.S. Uriah (1788 Feb 12)
Hunter, Andrew (1837 Feb 8)
Hupp, George F. (1837 Nov 1, Nov 25; 1838 Mar 22)
Huron, J. (1790 Oct 12; 1793 May 13)
Huston, Archibald W. (1838 Apr 24)
Hutchinson, Alexander (1819 Mar 2)
Irvine, James (1831 Jul 16)
Irvine, John (1822 Sep 21)
Irwin, Robert, Sr. (1798 Dec 24)